# TATIANE LEITE

www.tatileite.com 👓 tatiane.leite@gmail.com (310)733-0548

# SUMMARY OF **QUALIFICATIONS**

Eight years of experience in Computer Graphics.

Innovative and self-driven, with a patented idea in Brazil as result of a Master's degree.

Extremely versatile personality, transitions very well between different areas and enjoys to work in multi disciplinary environments.

> Spanish (intermediate); Portuguese (native).

## **SKILLS**

#### Software:

Maya, Photoshop, After Effects, Nuke, ZBrush, Avid, FinalCut, Adobe Premiere

Language: Java, Android, C, Python

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Scholarship Mary Pickford 2016

Patent in Brazil 🚥 Title: Improving the Attractiveness of Faces in Images Number: BR 10 2012 016227 0

Scholarship for Master's Program (2 years) - Sponsored by CAPES Foundation (Education Ministry of Brazil)

## **PUBLICATIONS**

SIBGRAPI 2015 - Conference on Graphics, Patterns and Images **Title:** Improving the Attractiveness of Faces in Images 🖘

WSCG10 - International Conference on Computer Graphics, Visualization and Computer Vision

Title: 3D Facial Animation for Mobile Devices 👓

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# **7 Generation Games** (CA, USA)

Jul 2016 - Now

# In Transit Feature Film (CA, USA)

Jul 2016 - Oct 2016

May 2016 - Jun 2016

Moonesta Short Film (CA, USA)

UCLA Extension (CA, USA)

Jan 2013 - Dec 2013

# **Venturus Technical Innovation**

Center (SP, Brazil) Oct 2008 - Jun 2010

Motorola (SP, Brazil)

Feb 2008 - Oct 2008

#### General Artist 👓

- Responsible for the design and graphical work of several games, from character creation and animation to branding assets and promos.
- Developed a portfolio of 2D animations and videos that either move the game story forward or explains math techniques for educational purposes.

- Responsible for assembling creatively all the layers of images, dialogue and music in order to create a powerful narrative.
- Collaborated closely with the director to understand the dramatic story line and build the rhythm, pace and tension desired for the scenes.

#### Digital Compositor and Animator ...

- Responsible for coming up with the easiest and fastest solution to create a VFX butterfly that would be a parody of a medical TV advertisement.
- Created the butterfly animation and composed it into the shots using techniques such as camera tracking, color correction, 3D layers and particles.

#### **Teaching Assistant**

- Responsible for setting up and operating audiovisual equipments; maintain a record of every student's attendance and deliveries; organize and label all deliveries and plan schedules for presentations.

#### **Software Engineer**

- Developed apps that use camera phone and image processing to perform different activities such as panoramas pictures, face warp, face detection.

#### **Software Developer**

- Testing and debugging mobile operating systems and new prototypes and bug.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Santa Monica College (CA, USA)

2015 - Present

Gnomon (CA, USA)

2014 - 2015

## UCLA Extension (CA, USA)

2012 - 2014

**University of Campinas** (SP, Brazil)

2010 - 2012

University of Campinas (SP, Brazil) Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

2003 - 2007

# **Animation Certificate**

GPA: 3.93

#### **Visual Effects Courses**

Compositing, Digital Sculpting, Maya Courses such as Character Animation and Modeling.

## **Certificate in Entertainment Studies**

Earned with distinction.

#### Master of Science in Computer Engineering ∞

Thesis: Enhancement of facial attractiveness in images.

# RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

# **CTNx Creative Talent Network Animation Expo** (Burbank, CA)

2015 and 2016

### **LABRFF Los Angeles Brazilian** Film Festival (Los Angeles, CA)

2015 and 2016

#### Volunteer

- Organizing and managing guest flow at venues; hosting and managing speakers, directing guests to correct lines and theaters.

#### Volunteer

- Assisting the event director with day-to-day planning for festival events and screenings.